Tissue Culture Association records
Tissue Culture Association records
- Series I. President, 1940-1985; bulk 1960-1984; 8960 items (13.5 linear feet)
  - Subseries I.A. Correspondence, 1940-1984; 7,600 items (11.25 linear feet)
    - Evans: Fell Division 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Evans: Film Committee 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Evans: Handbook of Policies and Procedures 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Evans: Human Value Committee 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Evans: Insurance (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Evans: International Science and Engineering Fair (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Evans: Kahn 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Evans: Kruse, Paul 1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Evans: Legal Matters 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Evans: Local Committees 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Evans: Manual 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Evans: Materials and Supplies Committee 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Evans: Michigan Branch 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Evans: Midwestern Branch 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Evans: NASA Liaison Committee 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Evans: Nardone 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Evans: Nardone 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Evans: Nardone 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Evans: National Medal of Science 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Evans: NMAC Proposals 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Evans: Noble Foundation 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Evans: Nominating Committee 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Evans: Officers 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Evans: Paul, John 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Evans: Placement Service 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Evans: Plant Division 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Evans: Program Committee 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Evans: Proposed Branches (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Evans: Publication Committee 1968-1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Evans: Publicity Committee 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Evans: Scholarship Fund 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Evans: Search Committee (Director of WAJSC) 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Evans: Sera Committee 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Evans: Staff 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Evans: Student Affairs 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Evans: Study Program 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Evans: Terminology Committee 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Evans: Tellers Committee 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Evans: Texas Branch 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Evans: WAJSC 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Kahn: General 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Kahn: General 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Kahn: American Type Culture Collection (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Kahn: Biological Stain Commission 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Kahn: Business Office 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - California Branch 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Kahn: Central States Branch 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Kahn: Chappel 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Kahn: Chemically Defined Media 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Kahn: Chemically Defined Media 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Kahn: Council 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Kahn: Earle Award 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Kahn: Editorial Committee 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Kahn: Education 1965-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Kahn: Education Committee 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Kahn: Etiologic Agents 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Kahn: Executive Board 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kahn: Fell Committee 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Kahn: Film Collection Committee 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Kahn: International Science Fair 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kahn: International Science and Engineering Fair 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kahn: Invertebrate Division 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Kahn: Manual Committee 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Kahn: Materials and Supplies 1968-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Kahn: Nardone (Sec.) 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Kahn: National Medal of Science 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kahn: National Medal of Science Advisory Center 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kahn: National Medal of Science Advisory Center 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Kahn: National Medal of Science Advisory Center 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Kahn: Membership (Sustaining) 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Kahn: Membership 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Kahn: Nomenclature Committee 1962-1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Kahn: Nominating Committee 1968-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Kahn: Oak Ridge Laboratory 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Kahn: Perry 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Kahn: Placement 1968-1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Kahn: Program Committee 1965-1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Kahn: Program Committee 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Kahn: Publication Committee 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kahn: Public Affairs Committte 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Kahn: Publicity Committee 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kahn: Search Committee 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Kahn: Sera and Contamination Committee 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kahn: Standardization, Collection and Distribution Committee 1961-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Kahn: Student Committee 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kahn: Terminology Committee 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Kahn: Toxicity Testing 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Kahn: Workshops 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Lennette: General 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Lennette: General 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Lennette: General 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Lennette: General 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Lennette: Acuff Associates 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lennette: Biology Alliance for Public Affairs 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Lennette: Committees ( Toxicity Testing in Vitro 1976) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Lennette: Council 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Lennette: Executive Board: 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Lennette: Form Letters (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Lennette: Fundraising/Development 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Lennette: Health Awards Banquet-International Science Fair 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Lennette: National Medical Audio Visual Center 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Lennette: Perry, Vernon (In Vitro editor) 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Lennette: Publicity Committee 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lennette: Secretary 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Lennette: Special Committee/ATCC (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Lennette: Special Committee/Biological Stain Commission 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Lennette: Special Committee/Business Office 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Lennette: Treasurer 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Lennette: Treasurer 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Porter: General 1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Porter: American cancer Society Proposal 1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Porter: American Type Culture Collection 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Porter: Awards Committee 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Porter: Cell and Tissue Banks 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Porter: Certification 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Porter: Certificates 1978 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Porter: Cailleau, Relda 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Porter: Douglas, William 1978 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Porter: Materials and Supplies 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Porter: Media Standardization 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Porter: Nelson-Rees Censure 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - McGarrity: General 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - McGarrity: Audio Visual Committee 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - McGarrity: Branches 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Carcinogenesis, Mutagenesis and Toxicity in Vitro 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Development and Promotion 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Education 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Miscellaneous 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Nominating 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Program (Meeting 1983) (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Publications (in Vitro 1982-1984) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - McGarrity: Committee/Reports 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - McGarrity: Council 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - McGarrity: Council Subcommittee 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - McGarrity: Divisions/Miscellaneous 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - McGarrity: Editorial Board 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - McGarrity: Executive Board 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - McGarrity: Executive Board 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - McGarrity: Historical Society Branch (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - McGarrity: Litigation 1983-984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - McGarrity: Reports 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - McGarrity: Special Committee on Litigation 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - McGarrity: Special Committee on Litigation (Documents Relating to the Conveyance of Deed of the WA Jones Cell Science Center) 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - McGarrity: Special Committee on Litigation 1983/5-6 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - McGarrity: Special Committee on Litigation 1983/6-1984-7 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - McGarrity: Standardization 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Sato: General 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sato: Business Office 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Sato: Decennial Review Conference 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Sato: Earle Award 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Sato: Education Committee 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Sato: Fell Division 1984 /td (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Sato: International Affiliation Committee 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Sato: Membership Renewal Procedures 1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Sato: Program Committee 1984 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Subseries I.B. Administrative Files, 1949-1984; 1,360 items (2.25 linear feet)
    Bylaws and constitution revisions are in date order and report files are in alpha order by type and in date order. Miscellaneous files are in alphabetical order.
    - Constitution and Bylaws 1949, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Constitutional Amendment Ballot 1953 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revisions 1963 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revisions 1964- 1965 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Correspondence 1971 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Responses of the Board of Governors 1971 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Federoff 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: General Correspondence 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Correspondence 1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Related Documents and Comments 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revision Drafts 1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Amended and Adopted 1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: General Correspondence 1974 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Resolutions 1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revisions 1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: Revisions 1975 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: 1980 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: General Correspondence 1983 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: General Correspondence 1984 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Incorporation Documents: 1964, 1967, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Reports: Annual 1969/6-1970/6 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Reports: Annual 1970/6-1971/6 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Reports: Annual 1971/6-1972/6 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Reports: Annual 1973/6-1974/6 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Reports: Annual 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Reports: Annual 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Reports: Annual 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Reports: Annual 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Reports: Annual Report to Council 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #1-19 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #19-85 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #86-124 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #125-163 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #164-190 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #201-228 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Reports: Annual/Notes and Draft Material #229-283 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Reports: President’s 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Reports: President’s 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Reports: Progress 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous: Administrative Calendar 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous: Form Letters and Addresses (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous: Handbook of Policy and Procedures 1973-974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous: National Visual Audio Center (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous: Rosters of Committees 1948-1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous: Rosters of Council and Committees 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous: Rosters of Executive Board Liaison Chart 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous: Rosters of Officers and Members at Large 1946-1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous: Rosters of Officers and Members at Large 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous: Tax Information (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Series II. Secretary, 1946-1982; 4540 items (6.75 linear feet)
  Series contains correspondence files, applications, reports, member lists, and rosters organized into two sub-series: Correspondence and Membership.
  - Subseries II.A. Correspondence, 1946-1978; 1,040 items (1.5 linear feet)
    Correspondence is arranged in the order of the Secretary that held office with general correspondence first, followed by subject files in alphabetical order.
    - Murray: General 1946 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Murray: General 1947/1-5 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Murray: General 1947/6-12 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Murray: General 1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Murray: 1949/1-9 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Murray: 1949/10-12 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Murray: 1950 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Murray: 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Murray: Bibliography 1947-1961 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Murray: Budget (Travel) 1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sidman: General 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Sidman: General 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Sidman: Film Library 1965-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kahn: General 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Kahn: Addressograph, Mailers 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Kahn: Annual Meetings 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Kahn: “A’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Kahn: “B’s” 1965-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Kahn: “C’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Kahn: “D’s” 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Kahn: “E’s” 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Kahn: “F’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Kahn: Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Kahn: “G’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Kahn: “H’s” 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Kahn: “I’s” 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Kahn: “J’s” 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Kahn: “K’s” 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Kahn: “L’s” 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Kahn: “M’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Kahn: “N’s” 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Kahn: “O’s” 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Kahn: “P’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Kahn: “R’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Kahn: “S’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Kahn: “T’s” 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Kahn: “U’s” 1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Kahn: “V’s” 1972 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Kahn: “ W’s”1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Kahn: “Z’s” 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Nardone: General 1972-1974 Part I (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Nardone: General 1972-1974 Part II (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Nardone: General 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Nardone: Chapple 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Nardone: Human Values 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Nardone: Potential Sustaining Members 1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Nardone: Sustaining Members 1974 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Subseries II.B. Membership, 1949-1982; 3,500 items (5.25 linear feet)
    Application forms, correspondence files, election ballots, member files, and rosters are arranged in alpha order by type of document.
    - Membership: Application Forms (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Membership: Application Lists (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Membership: Applications “A’s” (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Membership: Applications “B’s” (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Membership: Applications “C’s" /td (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Membership: Applications “D’s" (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Membership: Applications “E’s" (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Membership: Applications “F’s" (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Membership: Applications “G’s" /td (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Membership: Applications “H’s" (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Applications “I’s" (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Applications “J’s" (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Applications “K’s" (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Membership: Applications “L’s" (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Membership: Applications “M’s" (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Membership: Applications “N’s" (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Membership: Applications “O’s" (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Membership: Applications “P’s" (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Membership: Applications “Q’s" (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Membership: Applications “R’s" (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Membership: Applications “Sa-Sc" (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Membership: Applications “Se-Si" (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Membership: Applications “Sk-Sp" (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Membership: Applications “St-Sw" (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Membership: Applications “T’s" (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Membership: Applications “U’s" (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Membership: Applications “V’s" (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Membership: Applications “W’s" (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Membership: Applications “X, Y, Z’s" (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Membership: Charter Members (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Membership: Companies and Organizations (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Membership: Committee Correspondence 1966-1976 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Membership: Corresponding Members 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Membership: Emeritus 1966-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Membership: Honorary Members Elections Ballots 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Membership: Honorary Members 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Membership: Member Files A (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Membership: Member Files B (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Membership: Member Files Ca-Cl (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Membership: Member Files Co-Cu (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Member Files Da-De (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Member Files Di-Du (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Member Files Ea-El (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Membership: Member Files Em-Ev (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Membership: Member Files Fa-Fi (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Membership: Member Files Fl-Fu (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Membership: Member Files Ga-Go (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Membership: Member Files Gr-Gu (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Membership: Member Files Ha-He (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Membership: Member Files Hi-Hu (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Membership: Member Files I (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Membership: Member Files J (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Membership: Member Files K (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Membership: Member Files La-Le (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Membership: Member Files Li (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Member Files Lo-Lu (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Member Files Ma (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Member Files Mc (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Membership: Member Files Me-Mi (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Membership: Member Files Mo-Mu (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Membership: Member Files N (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Membership: Member Files O (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Membership: Member Files Pa (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Membership: Member Files Pe-Pu (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Membership: Member Files Q (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Membership: Member Files Ra-Re (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Membership: Member Files Ri-Rh (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Membership: Member Files Ro-Ru (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Membership: Member Files Sa-Sc (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Membership: Member Files Se-Si (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Membership: Member Files Sk-Su (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Membership: Member Files T (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Membership: Member Files U (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Membership: Member Files V (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Membership: Member Files W (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Membership: Member Files Y and Z (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Membership: Rosters 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Membership: Rosters 1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Membership: Rosters 1948 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Membership: Rosters 1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Membership: Rosters 1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Membership: Rosters 1951 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Membership: Rosters 1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Rosters 1953 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Rosters 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Rosters 1955 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Membership: Rosters 1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Membership: Rosters 1957 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Membership: Rosters 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Membership: Rosters 1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Membership: Rosters 1960 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Membership: Rosters 1961 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Membership: Rosters 1962 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Membership: Rosters 1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Membership: Rosters 1964 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Membership: Rosters 1965 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Membership: Rosters 1966 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Membership: Rosters 1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Membership: Rosters 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Membership: Rosters 1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Membership: Rosters 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Membership: Rosters 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Membership: Rosters 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Membership: Rosters 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Membership: Rosters 1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Membership: Rosters 1977 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Membership: Rosters 1980, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Membership: Rosters/Lost, Drooped, Resigned or Deceased 1948-1964 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Membership: Sustaining Members 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Membership: Sustaining Members 1973 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Membership: Sustaining Members 1976 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Membership: Sustaining Members 1977 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Membership: Sustaining Members 1978 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Series III. Treasurer, 1947-1980; 1300 items (2 linear feet)
  The Treasurer series contains correspondence, annual reports, audits, budgets, financial reports, general subject files and tax information. The series begins with correspondence followed by subject files arranged in alphabetical order by type of document and then date order.
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: General 1940-1963 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Film 1953-1959 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Gey 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Grants 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Honorary Members 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Infantile Paralysis 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Lewis, Warren 1953-1957 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence/Hetherington: Murray 1950-1956 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence: General 1971-176 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence/Hink: General 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 47)